感谢你Veto  现在我们要在手机上安装Sunshine这款应用程序
Thanks Veto. And now it's time to install the Sunshine app on our phones.
我们需要一根USB数据线连接手机
So to get started, let's grab a USB cable. We'll plug in our device and
然后我们需要启用USB调试  这个可以在手机的设置—
then we'll need to enable USB debugging. This can be found in Developer options
开发者选项中找到  但是需要注意的是  在Android4.2以上的版本里
in the Settings app. But note that on Android devices 4.2 and above,
这个选项默认是隐藏的  怎么找到它呢
the option is actually hidden by default. To find the secret menu,
到设置界面  拉到最下面选择关于手机
go to the Settings app. Scroll down to About phone.
找到Build number(版本号)
Then go down to Build number and
轻触七次之后
tap on that seven times [SOUND]. Then,
返回到设置界面  你就能看到开发者选项神奇的出现啦
when you go back to Settings, you'll see the Developer options menu appear.
同样的  你需要在电脑上安装驱动等让电脑识别你的设备  点击下面的链接
Also, set up your computer to detect your device. Check the instructor notes for
查看更多  我们在开发中将会用真机测试因为它相对更快
more details. We're going to continue using a device because it's faster and
更顺畅  但是如果尚未拥有一台Android设备
smoother for development. But if you don't have one,
木有问题  你可以用我们之前创建的模拟器来开发
that's okay. You can continue using the emulator that we created previously.